# **ISAAC B. CONTEH**

#### PRODUCT DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

0000



## **ABOUT ME**

I'm an enthusiastic and creative Product designer & Frontend Developer with industry experience. I am skilled at taking projects from ideation to development phase. I love widening my horizon and learning new technologies to fast-track my career

## **EDUCATION**

- Dele Peddle High School Sierra Leone (2011-2014)
- Limkokwing University Malaysia (2014-2018)

Bachelor's - Software Engineering with Multimedia CGPA: 3.76

## CONTACT/LINKS

- +23280710209
- zacflixx2917@gmail.com
- 6b Standford Drive, Freetown Sierra Leone
- https://isaac-29.netlify.app/
- https://www.behance.net/isaacconteh

## SKILLS

- UX Design: Wireframes, User journey maps etc
- UI Design & Prototype: Figma, XD, Sketch, Al ...
- Frontend Development HTML, Css, Js , Flutter ...
- CMS Development- Wordpress, Wix, Shopify ...
- Graphic Design Company graphics / advertisments
- Blogging and Creative content writing

## **EXPERIENCES**

#### **DIGITAL UX LEAD**, Vodafone

VODAFONE QATAR - Infinity Solutions Llc. OCT 2022 - Present

- Design best digital user experience for our Customers across all digital channels
- E2E user experience design of digital products & services based on service design methodology.
- · Creating content for the designed pages
- Use data analysis to iteratively improve the digital experience and campaign effectiveness.

#### FRONTEND SOFTWARE ENGINEER

GUARANTY TRUST BANK SIERRA LEONE APR 2022 - AUG 2022

- Design customer experience and user interface of company applications using design platforms like Figma and Sketch etc.
- Help develop the frontend code of approved Ui-Ux of company applications.
- Design basic company brand graphics/corporate advertisements and maintain website

#### **UI DESIGNER & DEVELOPER**

TAMAWAL INC. SAUDI ARABIA JUL 2021 - MAR 2022

- Designing company website pages and mobile application
- Develop the frontend code of approved designsAchievement - Successfully lunched the company's Ltr-Rtl Website and Customer Dashboard (www.tamawal.sa)
- Responsible for the design of company graphics and advertisements

#### **WEB DESIGN INTERN**

CSI PROPERTIES - MALAYSIA AUG 2021 - NOV 2021

- Tasked with revamping the official company website built on Wordpress (https://csiprop.com/)
- · Video and Photo editing for official content
- Other basic IT task